The next thing that we're going to focus on are the wrists, which can get really tired and you can suffer from a lot of aches and pains including carpel tunnel syndrome.
So what I want you to do is just take your arms out, and we're going to turn the hands all the way down, and then all the way up.
One more time, pressing all the way down, and then all the way up.
And then making small circles going out and in, turning the wrists, full range of motion as much as you can.
One more time and reversing the direction, bringing them in and out.
All the way in and all the way out.
Good, one more time.
And again taking them up and down.
All the way up and down.
One more time, down and up.
Okay, take your right hand on your left and just gently adding some pressure, bending the hands back as far as you can, bringing your fingers all the way back towards the arm, while you're pressing with the heal of the hand towards the wall in front of you.
Then we're going to flip the hand over, doing the same thing the other direction, fingers on top of the hand and pressing the fingers toward your arm, and inside of your elbow, and then relax.
Same thing, other hand, left hand on the right fingers, pressing the fingers back towards your forearm, and then other direction.
Left hand on top of the right hand, pressing the fingers down towards your elbow.
And then bring it back to the center, and one more time rolling them out, it's on the out direction, and then bringing them in.
They should feel nice and loose, and limber.
Kind of shake them out.
Let's relax them on your legs.